var questions = [
// each object holds a question property and answer property
// the correct answer will always be place first at index 0 of the answer array
	{	question: "What is the most important part of programming?",
		answers: ["Taking the first step.",
				"Knowing how to code.",
				"Being a certified programmer.",
				"Learning everything their is to know about programming."]
	},

	{	question: "What is the primary use of regular expressions?",
		answers: ["Validation by searching for patterns.",
				"Expressions used on a regular bases.",
				"Checks for regular conditions in the function of the code.",
				"Regulates expressions."]
},

	{	question: "What does a switch do?",
		answers: ["Takes in a single variable and checks it against multiple conditions for different outputs.",
				"Turns on the lights.",
				"Switch from one function to the next.",
				"Turn off your computer."]
	},

	{	question: "What is a good use of Objects when programming?",
		answers: ["Act as a container for all variables and functions.",
				"To provide visual inspiration.",
				"To provide support.",
				"Paper weights."]
	},

	{	question: "What is a local variable?",
		answers: ["A variable that is part of a function definition.",
				"A variable that changes with the local community.",
				"A variable named local.",
				"A variable that can be accessed on your local computer."]
	},

	{	question: "What is a global variable?",
		answers: ["A variable that can be access by any function that scope extends to the window object.",
				"A variable that can be accessed around the globe.",
				"A variable that changes depending on the region of the world where you live.",
				"A variable named global."]
	},

	{	question: "What is the main purpose of if statements?",
		answers: ["Provide conditional checks within there scope.",
				"Wrap entire functions.",
				"Allow else statements to be used",
				'A wish like, "If I had a million dollars".']
		},

	{	question: "What is a good use of for loops?",
		answers: ["Cloning array values.",
				"Running programs in endless cycles.",
				"Practicing your golf swing.",
				"Generating console.log's."]
	},

	{	question: "What is one way to increase the scope of a function?",
		answers: ["Create a reference to the object you wish to grant access inside the scope.",
				"Extend a pipe.",
				"Use class functions to increase the scope.",
				'Make use of key word "self".']
	},

	{	question: "What is scope?",
		answers: ["The referencing range of a function.",
				 "A mouth wash.", 
				 "An object used to see long distance's.",
				 'The key word "this".'],
	}
] // end of the questions array